var SectionA = [
{"question":"When does a third class medical certificate expire?","answer":" FAR 61.23 If you are under the age of 40, it will expire 60 months on the last day of the that it was issued. If you are over 40 years of age, then it will expire 24 months on the last day of the month that it was issued."},
{"question":"What are the categories of aircraft w.r.t. certification of airmen purposes?","answer":"Airplane, rotorcraft, glider, lighter-than-air LARG"},
{"question":"What are the airplane classes w.r.t. certification of airmen purposes?","answer":" SEL,MEL,SES, MES"},
{"question":"Wha are the rotorcraft classes w.r.t. certification of airmen purposes?","answer":" Helicopter, gyrocopter"},
{"question":"What are the lighter-than-air classes w.r.t. certification fo airmen tpurposes?","answer":"airship, free balloon hot air balloon gas balloon"},
{"question":"What are the categories of aircraft w.r.t certification of airmen purposes?","answer":" Transport, utility, normal, experimental, restricted, acrobatic, provisional TUNERAP"},
{"question":"What are teh recency of flight experience requirements for day time flights?","answer":" FAR 61.57 To carry passengers, you must have made three landings and three takeoffs within the preceding 90 days in an aircraft of the same category, class, and type as the one in which passengeres are to be carried. The landings must be to a full stop if the airplane has a tailwheel."},
{"question":"What are teh recency of flight experience requirements for night time flights?","answer":" FAR 61.57 No person may act as pilot in command of an aircraft carrying passengers during th eperiod beginning 1 hr after sunset and ending 1hr before sunrise, unless within the preceding 90 days that person has made at least three full stop landing and three takeoffs during said time period in the same category, class, and type."},
{"question":"What is a high performance airplane?","answer":"It is defined as an airplane with more than 200 hp."},
{"question":"What is a complex airplane?","answer":" A complex airplane has retractable landing gear, flaps, and a controllable pitch propeller."}]